Guide to the A. B. Cook Papers 1882-1940
Montana Historical Society Archives
- A.B. Cook
  - General Correspondence
    - W.E. Chapman (Riparia, Wash.), 1925-1928 (Box-folder 4 / 16)
    - Chester Charlton (Bridesville, B.C.), 1917, 1927-1928 (Box-folder 4 / 17)
    - Chicago, Milwaukee and Puget Sound Railway (includes claims for cattle killed), 1914-1928 (Box-folder 4 / 18-19)
    - Chicago (correspondents include Chicago and North Western Railway Company; Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad Company; Chicago Live Stock Exchange), 1910-1928 (Box-folder 4 / 20)
    - H.W. Child (Helena, Mont.), 1915-1924 (Box-folder 4 / 21)
    - A.M. Chisholm (re Butte, Mont. property), 1926 (Box-folder 4 / 22)
    - Ch-Ci (correspondents include H.D. Chapman, R.B. Chappell, Edd Chase, Chase National Bank, L. Chatterton, Chauncey Wright Restaurant Company, W.W. Cheely, Chewacan Land and Cattle Company, Carl A. Church, Citizens National Bank), 1910-1928 (Box-folder 4 / 23)
    - Clapp, Norstrom and Riley (Minneapolis, Minn.), 1909-1921 (Box-folder 4 / 24)
    - Alfred H. Clarke (Flying H Ranch), 1923-1926 (Box-folder 4 / 25)
    - John Clay and Company, 1919-1928 (Box-folder 4 / 26-28)
    - Clay, Robinson and Company, 1914-1920 (Box-folder 5 / 1)
    - Cliff Clevenger (Dallas, Pa.), 1921-1927 (Box-folder 5 / 2)
    - Clinton Falls Nursery Company (Owatonna, Minn.), 1926-1928 (Box-folder 5 / 3)
    - Cl (correspondents include H. Earl Clack Company, K.A. Clark, Sheldon Clark, K.S. Cleveland, Climax Corporation, Ralph Close), 1904-1928 (Box-folder 5 / 4)
    - Collins Land Company; Jeremiah Collins (re land scrip), 1916-1926 (Box-folder 5 / 5)
    - P.M. Collins (Toronto, Ont.), 1912 (Box-folder 5 / 6)
    - Columbia Basin Wool Warehouse Company, 1918-1921 (Box-folder 5 / 7)
    - F.T. Colver (Mocassin Mountain Stock Ranch, Brooks, Mont.), 1927-1928 (Box-folder 5 / 8)
    - Frank Conley (Deer Lodge, Mont.), 1921-1928 (Box-folder 5 / 9)
    - F.B. Connelly Company (Billings, Mont.), 1918-1926 (Box-folder 5 / 10)
    - Continental Oil Company, 1918-1928 (Box-folder 5 / 11)
    - Frank Hervey Cook, 1920-1928 (Box-folder 5 / 12)
    - Mary A. Cook, 1912-1924 (Box-folder 5 / 13)
    - Cook [non-relatives], 1912-1928 (Box-folder 5 / 14)
    - Cook, Deeks, Hinds and Company [predecessor of Cook Construction Company], 1907-1909 (Box-folder 5 / 15)
    - Cook Stock Farm / A.B. Cook Stock Farms (Ivan Davis), 1917-1918 (Box-folder 5 / 16)
    - Cook Stock Farm / A.B. Cook Stock Farms (Frances Firkey), 1923 (Box-folder 5 / 17)
    - Cook Stock Farm / A.B. Cook Stock Farms (C.D. Hall), 1925-1928 (Box-folder 5 / 18)
    - Cook Stock Farm / A.B. Cook Stock Farms (Axel Holmstrom), 1917-1928 (Box-folder 5 / 19-23)
    - Cook Stock Farm / A.B. Cook Stock Farms (Iver Holth), 1923-1926 (Box-folder 6 / 1)
    - Cook Stock Farm / A.B. Cook Stock Farms (H.S. Hov, includes inventory of ranch house at Dunleavy Ranch), 1916-1918 (Box-folder 6 / 2)
    - Cook Stock Farm / A.B. Cook Stock Farms (H.B. Shoop, auditor), 1917 (Box-folder 6 / 3)
    - Cook Stock Farm / A.B. Cook Stock Farms (Mae Sim; Mae Simpkins), 1919, 1925 (Box-folder 6 / 4)
    - Cook Stock Farm / A.B. Cook Stock Farms (George Sim), 1915-1919, 1922 (Box-folder 6 / 5-10)
    - Cook Stock Farm / A.B. Cook Stock Farms (Grace Van Winkle), 1926-1928 (Box-folder 6 / 11)
    - Cook Stock Farm / A.B. Cook Stock Farms (telegrams), 1916-1919, n.d. (Box-folder 6 / 12-14)
    - Coomac Oil Fields, Ltd. (Thomas H. Rea) [maps in OVERSIZE FOLDER 1], 1914-1918 (Box-folder 6 / 15)
    - Cooper (correspondents include Charles H. Cooper, E.N. Cooper, Hugh L. Cooper, Stuart Cooper), 1921-1928 (Box-folder 6 / 16)
    - H.D. Cornish (Cornish and Patten, Osborn, Mo.), 1909 (Box-folder 6 / 17)
    - C.N. Cosgrove (Minnesota Valley Canning Company), 1921-1925 (Box-folder 6 / 18)
    - Co (correspondents include Coffin Brothers, Robert H. Cole, Coleman and Reitze, F.V.H. Collins, Commercial National Bank, Condon Commission Company, J.D. Conrad, Robert H. Cosgrove), 1909-1928 (Box-folder 7 / 1)
    - Cr (correspondents include Crane and Ordway Company, Harry C. Cranke, J.W. Crawford, Burke H. Critchfield, L.L. Crockett, J.C. Cronk, Harry Cross, Oscar Crutchfield), 1909-1928 (Box-folder 7 / 2)
    - Curtis Publishing Company, 1919-1922 (Box-folder 7 / 3)
    - Cu (correspondents include O.E. Culbert, William A. Culbertson, Cunningham Sheep Company), 1909-1928 (Box-folder 7 / 4)
    - Dallman and Cooper Supply Company (Fond du Lac, Wisc.), 1918-1923 (Box-folder 7 / 5)
    - J.F. Dauterman (Alder, Mont.), 1928 (Box-folder 7 / 6)
    - John F. Davies (Butte, Mont.), 1908-1917 (Box-folder 7 / 7)
    - Davis (correspondents include Donald D. Davis, Harry C. Davis, M.E. Davis, Mrs. Perry Davis, Russell S. Davis), 1914-1926 (Box-folder 7 / 8)
    - Da (correspondents include A. Danielson, Fred Dart, A.F. Daughenbaugh, Mabel Davidson, John Day), 1909-1928 (Box-folder 7 / 9)
    - Deeks and Deeks, Contractors (re dissolution of partnership with Cook), 1909 (Box-folder 7 / 10)
    - Deere and Webber Company; John Deere and Company, 1911, 1922-1928 (Box-folder 7 / 11)
    - Denver Joint Stock Land Bank (Harry Henderson), 1924-1928 (Box-folder 7 / 12)
    - Denver Union Stockyards, 1916, 1923 (Box-folder 7 / 13)
    - De-Di (correspondents include Elmer Deebach, Deer Lodge Farms Company, DeLaval Separator Company, Delaware Land and Development Company, Denver Record-Stockman, W.A. Depuy, DeRicqles Agency, W.P. Devereux Company, F.W. Dickey, H.N. Dion), 1912-1928 (Box-folder 7 / 14)
    - John O. Donovan (Butte, Mont.), 1922-1926 (Box-folder 7 / 15)
    - Double L Bar Ranch (Glen Billings and Una Kaufman, Cody, Wyo.), 1928 (Box-folder 7 / 16)
    - Do (correspondents include James Dodd, J.A. Doherty, George Doi, W.H. Donald, Dooley Brothers, Samuel R. Douglas, Lee F. Doyle), 1909-1928 (Box-folder 7 / 17)
    - Drexel State Bank of Chicago, 1923-1928 (Box-folder 7 / 18)
    - W.S. Dudley (Kentucky River Coal Corporation), 1925-1928 (Box-folder 7 / 19)
    - Dr-Dy (correspondents include F.W. Drake, J. Sterling Drake, A.W. DuBois, W.D. Duke, Charles Dumont, G. Dupont, Pierre Duryea, Paul Dysart), 1914-1928 (Box-folder 7 / 20)
    - Eads Live Stock Company (Rolla P. Heren, Eads, Colo.), 1924-1928 (Box-folder 7 / 21)
    - Eaton's Ranch (Wolf, Wyo.), 1923-1928 (Box-folder 7 / 22)
    - J.E. Edwards (Forsyth, Mont.), 1911-1925 (Box-folder 7 / 23)
    - J.H. Empson (Helena, Mont.), 1917-1924 (Box-folder 7 / 24)
    - John M. Evans (U.S. Representative), 1925-1927 (Box-folder 7 / 25)
    - Exemption Board (re World War I draft), 1918 (Box-folder 7 / 26)
    - E (correspondents include Eastern Montana Ranches Inc., James Eckford, V.T. Edmunds, Adolph H. Eiselein, Eldorado Cooperative Canal Company, Electric Wheel Company, Bessie M. Elliott, J.C. Epperson, John Etchart), 1909-1928 (Box-folder 7 / 27)
    - Farmers Advocate and Home Journal, 1918-1920 (Box-folder 8 / 1)
    - Farwell, Ozman, Kirk and Company, 1909-1925 (Box-folder 8 / 2)
    - Fa (correspondents include Thomas Fagan; Douglas Fairbanks; Fairbanks, Morse and Company; Farm and Ranch Review; Farmer and Breeder; John H. Farmer; Farmers and Mechanics Savings Bank of Minneapolis; Farmers and Miners State Bank; Farmers' Magazine; L.L. Farr; Frank Farrar), 1909-1928 (Box-folder 8 / 3)
    - Federal Land Bank of Spokane, 1925-1928 (Box-folder 8 / 4)
    - W.M. Ferguson (Hysham, Mont.), 1925-1926 (Box-folder 8 / 5)
    - Fe (correspondents include Federal Machinery and Equipment Company, Robert Feigel, Fenner and Beane, Fergus County), 1917-1926 (Box-folder 8 / 6)
    - The Field and El Campo (published by Advanced Agricultural Publishing Company and American International Publishing Company; A.B. Cook served on board), 1915-1928 (Box-folder 8 / 7-9)
    - Field and Stream, 1917-1928 (Box-folder 8 / 10)
    - First National Bank (many different towns and cities), 1908-1928 (Box-folder 8 / 11)
    - Fitzsimmons-Pierce-Frick Live Stock Commission Company, 1920-1921 (Box-folder 8 / 12)
    - Fi (correspondents include A.B. Ficke, James S. Finlen, First Congregational Church of Billings, J.U. Fish, Lawrence L. Fisher), 1908-1928 (Box-folder 8 / 13)
    - George P. Flannery (includes Alexander McLean Estate), 1909-1924 (Box-folder 8 / 14)
    - Fl (correspondents include John J. Fleming, J.H. Flick Construction Company, H.J. Flint, Alvah B. Flood, Harry L. Fluke), 1912-1927 (Box-folder 8 / 15)
    - Shirley S. Ford (Great Falls National Bank), 1917-1926 (Box-folder 8 / 16)
    - Vincent Fortune (re Oregon and Washington timber land), 1907 (Box-folder 8 / 17)
    - Fo (correspondents include John Forbis, Forestvale Cemetery Association, Walter S. Fortiner, Four Wheel Drive Auto Company, Fowler Serum Company), 1907-1928 (Box-folder 8 / 18)
    - Charles Friend and Son (St. Paul, Minn.), 1921-1928 (Box-folder 8 / 19)
    - H.B. Fulmer (P.K. Ranch, Sheridan, Wyo.), 1926-1928 (Box-folder 8 / 20)
    - Fr-Fu (correspondents include H.A. Frank, D.G. Frame, Franklin Paint Company, Ed Franz, Ed A. Fraser, O.G. Frederick, F.W. Friend, Peter Fuhrman), 1907, 1911-1928 (Box-folder 8 / 21)
    - Albert J. Galen (Helena, Mont.), 1920-1928 (Box-folder 8 / 22)
    - James L. Galen (Seattle, Wash.), 1912-1927 (Box-folder 8 / 23)
    - P.N. Gallaher (Basin, Wyo.), 1911 (Box-folder 8 / 24)
    - Goelet Gallatin (Big Horn, Wyo.), 1928 (Box-folder 8 / 25)
    - John and Nelson Gallinger (Leedy, Mont.), 1923-1928 (Box-folder 8 / 26)
    - H.C. Gardiner (Mount Haggin Land and Livestock Company, Anaconda Copper Mining Company), 1909-1927 (Box-folder 8 / 27)
    - C.R. Garner and Company (Amarillo, Tex.), 1914-1927 (Box-folder 8 / 28)
    - Ga-Ge (correspondents include G.O.S. Cattle Company, John Gaffke, A.S. Gage, Gallatin Valley Milling Company, Warren Gammon and Son, E.D. Gantt, Dan Garrison, Gary Hay and Grain Company, Geary Brothers, C.H. Gerber, Gerlach-Barklow Company), 1910-1928 (Box-folder 8 / 29)
    - Edgar Gibson (Great Falls, Mont.), 1925-1927 (Box-folder 8 / 30)
    - W.H. Gleason (Kalispell, Mont.), 1926 (Box-folder 8 / 31)
    - Gi-Gl (correspondents include Walter C. Giebel, Gilchrist Brothers, Louis Gilger, Chester Glass, L.D. Glenn, Globe Serum Company), 1909-1928 (Box-folder 8 / 32)
    - Godfrey and Burdick Live Stock Commission (Helena, Mont.), 1910 (Box-folder 8 / 33)
    - Goldberg Hide and Fur Company; Goldberg Fur Company; Leo M. Goldberg Fur and Wool House (Helena, Mont.), 1916-1928 (Box-folder 9 / 1)
    - Sam Goodman (Helena, Mont.), 1917 (Box-folder 9 / 2)
    - Gordon and Ferguson (furs, St. Paul, Minn.), 1921-1926 (Box-folder 9 / 3)
    - Gover's Strain of S.C. White Leghorns (Denver, Colo.), 1920-1921 (Box-folder 9 / 4)
    - Sam D. Goza (Helena, Mont.), 1910-1927 (Box-folder 9 / 5)
    - Go (correspondents include O.F. Goddard, Leonard Goettlich, Wallace and E.G. Good, J.A. Gordon), 1909-1928 (Box-folder 9 / 6)
    - Grain Growers' Guide, 1918-1920 (Box-folder 9 / 7)
    - Duncan A. Grant (Tofino, B.C.), 1922-1923 (Box-folder 9 / 8)
    - Great Northern Railway Company, 1909-1928 (Box-folder 9 / 9)
    - Great Western Sugar Company, 1918-1923 (Box-folder 9 / 10)
    - H.P. Griffin (Belgrade, Mont.), 1911-1928 (Box-folder 9 / 11)
    - Gr (correspondents include George M. Grace, Graham Scientific Breeding School, Greater North Dakota Association, Green Meadow Farm, Greenfield Advertising Agency, Charles D. Greenfield, H.P. Greenough, Ulysses Gribble, Ben Groseclose, P.M. Gross, G.W. Grutz), 1915-1928 (Box-folder 9 / 12)
    - Milton S. Gunn (Helena, Mont.), 1912-1925 (Box-folder 9 / 13-15)
    - Gu-Gy (correspondents include Samuel R. Guard, F.P. Guidry, Arthur Guiterman enclosing poem re William Gibbs McAdoo, Gypsum Industries), 1919-1928 (Box-folder 9 / 16)
    - Haggart Construction Company (Fargo, N.D.), 1918-1926 (Box-folder 9 / 17)
    - Herbert Haight (Suffolk, Mont.), 1918-1928 (Box-folder 9 / 18)
    - H.E. Haley and Company (investments), 1918 (Box-folder 9 / 19)
    - W.H. Hall (Butte, Mont.), 1913-1915 (Box-folder 9 / 20)
    - Joseph A. Hanlon (Billings, Mont.), 1922-1925 (Box-folder 9 / 21)
    - Julius Hansen (Missoula, Mont.), 1913 (Box-folder 9 / 22)
    - Haa-Han (correspondents include John H. Haak, Charles Hageman, George W. Haggard, Charles S. Hale, Henry M. Halff, E.H. Halloway, Hamilton Farm, W.E. Hamilton, R.F. Hanks), 1907-1928 (Box-folder 9 / 23)
    - Richard A. Harlow (Moore and Lewistown, Mont.), 1917-1928 (Box-folder 9 / 24)
    - Har-Haz (correspondents include Hardesty Manufacturing Company, F.W. Harding re Toliver Placer, Harding Memorial Association, A.L. Harris, Clifford B. Harris, Haskell Institute, A.J. Haubert, Charles E. Havener, A.E. Hawes, Hawkeye Lightning Rod Company, Glenn G. Hayes, Pat Hayes), 1910-1928 (Box-folder 9 / 25)
    - William Randolph Hearst; Hearst Corporation (San Simeon, Calif.), 1921-1927 (Box-folder 9 / 26)
    - R.P. Heidrish (Whitehall, Mont.), 1927-1928 (Box-folder 9 / 27)
    - F. Augustus Heinze (Butte, Mont.), 1906-1912 (Box-folder 9 / 28)
    - Helena, City of, 1909-1926 (Box-folder 9 / 29)
    - Helena Commercial Club [blueprint map of Great Northern Park in OVERSIZE FOLDER 1], 1914 (Box-folder 9 / 30)
    - Helena (correspondents include Helena Automatic Telephone Company, Helena Clearing House Association, Helena Country Club, Helena Good Roads Association, Helena Power Transmission Company, Helena Skookum Chix Hatcheries), 1907-1928 (Box-folder 9 / 31)
    - Charles W. Helmick (Helena, Mont.), 1921-1925 (Box-folder 9 / 32)
    - Thomas H. Herrin (Helena, Mont.), 1918-1921 (Box-folder 9 / 33)
    - P.T. Hervin (Great Falls, Mont.), 1913-1917 (Box-folder 9 / 34)
    - He (correspondents include Healey and Company, L.E. Heaton, C.B. Heinemeyer, Oscar Hemgren, Harry B. Henderson, Walter S. Henderson, Henningsen Land Company, Charles B Herrick, Charles E. Herron, J.K. Hessey, J.J. Hetherington), 1906-1928 (Box-folder 9 / 35)
    - Robert F. Hildebrand (photographer of animals), 1917-1924 (Box-folder 10 / 1)
    - Albert Hill (Alexandria, S.D.), 1916-1919 (Box-folder 10 / 2)
    - C.P. Hill (Montreal, Que., includes report on Western Virginia coal property), 1917-1919 (Box-folder 10 / 3)
    - William Hislop (Hislop Sheep Company, Spokane, Wash.), 1917-1923 (Box-folder 10 / 4)
    - Hi (correspondents include D.J. Hickey, George F.H. Hicks, Highland Livestock Company, Roland Hill, S.T.H. Hill, Walter J. Hill, Hillandale Farm, A.F. Hinricks), 1909-1928 (Box-folder 10 / 5)
    - Hoar Shovel Company, 1926 (Box-folder 10 / 6)
    - T.D. Hobart (Pampa, Tex., includes Mrs. C. Adair Estate), 1924-1928 (Box-folder 10 / 7)
    - G.A. Hoepfner (Wallace Ranch, Jens, Mont.), 1918-1927 (Box-folder 10 / 8)
    - Orlin Holcomb (H.O. Ranch, Rapid City, S.D.), 1926 (Box-folder 10 / 9)
    - A.M. Holter Hardware Company (Helena, Mont.), 1913-1928 (Box-folder 10 / 10)
    - Horse Association of America, 1921-1928 (Box-folder 10 / 11)
    - John Hoy (re politics), 1921-1925 (Box-folder 10 / 12)
    - Ho (correspondents include Hoard's Dairyman, Robert V. Hoffman, J.C. Holbert, T.B. Holker, H.E. Holroyd, Holt Manufacturing Company, William L. Hoopes, Herbert Hoover, Andrew W. Hopkins, Royal E. House, D.M. Howard, Frank D. Howard), 1909-1928 (Box-folder 10 / 13)
    - F.R. Hudson (Elkhorn, Mont.), 1927-1928 (Box-folder 10 / 14)
    - Mark Hunt (Willow Spring Farm, White Sulphur Springs, Mont.), 1918-1924 (Box-folder 10 / 15)
    - George E. Hurd (Great Falls, Mont., re Diamond Bar Ranches Company and Diamond Ranch Company), 1921-1927 (Box-folder 10 / 16)
    - Hygeia Ice Company (Montreal, Que., includes Carlos Warfield), 1913 (Box-folder 10 / 17)
    - Hu-Hy (correspondents include Howard G. Huber, Wallis Huidekoper, W.A. Huff, W.W. Hulce, Hun Foo, W.S. Hunnewell, Sherman Hunt, W.G. Hunter, W.S. Hunter, W.W. Huntsberger, J.W. Hurd, Lewis S. Hurtig, M.G. Hutchins), 1910-1928 (Box-folder 10 / 18)
    - Idaho Agricultural Experiment Station, 1918-1926 (Box-folder 10 / 19)
    - Arthur W. Ide (Helena, Mont.), 1907 (Box-folder 10 / 20)
    - International (correspondents include International Anna Maud Hallam Clubs of Practical Psychology, International Belgian Horse Show, International Harvester Company, International Live Stock Exposition), 1915-1925 (Box-folder 10 / 21)
    - I (correspondents include Improved Clip Company, Industrial Locating Corporation, Inter-Mountain Fair, Inter-Mountain Milling Company, Inter-Southern Oil and Refining Company, Iowa State College, Elizabeth Ireland, Charles Irvine, William Irvine, Kenneth Ischs, Hal B. Ives), 1913-1928 (Box-folder 10 / 22)
    - James Manufacturing Company (re new barn), 1918 (Box-folder 10 / 23)
    - Wendell Jardine (Jardine Hot Springs, Jackson, Mont.), 1925-1926 (Box-folder 10 / 24)
    - Ja-Je (correspondents include Jackson [Miss.] Board of Trade, Newton Jacobson, George J. Jaeger, B.A. Jahn, Ernest Jarvis, Ella Jens, George Jeppesen), 1915-1928 (Box-folder 10 / 25)
    - John Johanson case (re First National Bank of Libby), 1926 (Box-folder 10 / 26)
    - Johnson (correspondents include A.R. Johnson, Eric Johnson, Jake Johnson, P.P. Johnson, Wilfred Johnson), 1909-1928 (Box-folder 10 / 27)
    - A.P. Johnston (Superior, Mont.), 1906-1907 (Box-folder 10 / 28)
    - Clarence H. Johnston, Architect (re ranch house) [architectural drawings in OVERSIZE FOLDER 2], 1915, 1918 (Box-folder 10 / 29)
    - Johnston (correspondents include Johnston and Ward Investments, James H. Johnston, Lawrence Johnston, Fred Johnston), 1921-1928 (Box-folder 10 / 30)
    - H.F. Jones (Butte, Mont. re Lexington Mine), 1917-1918 (Box-folder 10 / 31)
    - Jones (correspondents include Earl T. Jones, Frank Jones, Garnet G. Jones, J.F. Jones Lumber Company, Robert N. Jones, Thomas Jones, W.T. Jones), 1921-1928 (Box-folder 10 / 32)
    - Jo-Ju (correspondents include Jockey Club, Johns- Manville Company, John Jonas, W.J. Jordan, G.R. Jowell, Judson Freight Forwarding Company), 1915-1928 (Box-folder 10 / 33)
    - Kansas Blackleg Serum Company, 1919, 1925-1927 (Box-folder 11 / 1)
    - Ka (correspondents include Kansas City Club, Kansas City Journal-Post, Kaul Lumber Company), 1916, 1927-1928 (Box-folder 11 / 2)
    - Ken-Caryl Ranch Company (Littleton, Colo., includes Frank J. Smith, Margaret Kimmel), 1924-1926 (Box-folder 11 / 3)
    - John B. Kendrick (U.S. Senator, Wyoming), 1918-1928 (Box-folder 11 / 4)
    - Fred I. Ker (Hamilton, Ont.), 1922-1927 (Box-folder 11 / 5)
    - Harry H. Keyes (Armour Leather Company, Chicago, Ill.), 1924-1925 (Box-folder 11 / 6)
    - Ke (correspondents include J.S. Keerl, Frank Kelly, P.J. Kelly, Charles E. Kendall, E.M. Kennedy, J.E. Kennedy, Kentucky Tobacco Products Company), 1909-1928 (Box-folder 11 / 7)
    - J.C. Kinzer, Hartland Farm (Versailles, Ky., see also American Hereford Cattle Breeders Association), 1921-1928 (Box-folder 11 / 8)
    - Finor[?] Kirschbaum (White Sulphur Springs, Mont.), 1917 (Box-folder 11 / 9)
    - Frank Kirscher (Twete, Mont.), 1924-1926 (Box-folder 11 / 10)
    - Ki-Kl (correspondents include W.E. Kierstead, Charles Killick, Peter Killorn, J.W. Kilpatrick, Richard R. Kilroy, Tom King, Mrs. Hugh Kirkendall, John Klippstein, George S. Klotz), 1908-1928 (Box-folder 11 / 11)
    - M.E. Knowles; Knowles Veterinary Supply Company (Helena, Mont.), 1906-1926 (Box-folder 11 / 12)
    - Charles C. Krug (Marsh, Mont.), 1925-1926 (Box-folder 11 / 13)
    - Kn-Ky (correspondents include Kenneth Knight, A.J. Knollin, Edward Knowles, R.R. Kreps), 1913-1928 (Box-folder 11 / 14)
    - Thaddeus S. Lane (Spokane, Wash., see also Montana Independent Telephone Company subgroup), 1913-1927 (Box-folder 11 / 15)
    - Edwin Lausier (Bridgeport, Conn., New York, N.Y.), 1906-1928 (Box-folder 11 / 16)
    - La (correspondents include Carl Laemmle, Lake Superior Loader Company, G.E. Lane, George Lane and Company, Ltd., H.L. Lantz, Alfred Lapier, John LaPorte, Henry Larson, Jack Lawrence, Oliver C. Lawson, Layne and Bowler Company), 1924-1928 (Box-folder 11 / 17)
    - Scott Leavitt (U.S. Representative), 1924-1928 (Box-folder 11 / 18)
    - William LeBorious (Illinois Steel Bridge Company; Stiles Ranch), 1921-1927 (Box-folder 11 / 19)
    - LeClare and Cruse; A.F. LeClare (Missoula, Mont.), 1921-1924 (Box-folder 11 / 20)
    - Charles R. Leonard (Butte, Mont.), 1921-1923 (Box-folder 11 / 21)
    - Le (correspondents include W.T. Leahy, Robert G. Leavitt, B. Leopold Furs, George M. Lewis, Lon I. Lewis, Lewistown Chamber of Commerce), 1914-1928 (Box-folder 11 / 22)
    - Liberty Storage and Warehouse Company (New York, N.Y. re shipment of Mrs. Cook's household goods), 1909, 1917, 1919 (Box-folder 11 / 23)
    - Louis Lienemann (Butte, Mont.), 1924-1926 (Box-folder 11 / 24)
    - Live Stock Photo Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1924-1928 (Box-folder 11 / 25)
    - D.O. Lively (Panama-Pacific International Exposition), 1915-1917 (Box-folder 11 / 26)
    - Li (correspondents include Lindsay Helena Company, C. August Linn, Livestock Service, Livingston and Company), 1909-1928 (Box-folder 11 / 27)
    - J.B. Long and Company (Great Falls, Mont., includes R.F. Clary), 1909-1928 (Box-folder 11 / 28)
    - Louden Machinery Company (St. Paul, Minn.), 1915-1928 (Box-folder 11 / 29)
    - Frank Lowden (Oregon, Ill., includes presidential candidacy, 1928), 1921-1928 (Box-folder 11 / 30)
    - Lo-Ly (correspondents include R.N. Lodge, Long-Bell Lumber Company, H.C. Lookabaugh Oil Company, Frederick Loomis, Lowell Brothers and Talbott, M.K. Luther, Frederick B. Lynch, Lyon Iron Works), 1914-1928 (Box-folder 11 / 31)
    - Murdo Mackenzie (Boston Cattle Company, National Live Stock Shippers League, Matador Land and Cattle Company), 1921-1927 (Box-folder 11 / 32)
    - Fletcher Maddox (Great Falls, Mont.), 1911, 1921 (Box-folder 11 / 33)
    - D. Magee's Sons, Ltd., Hatters and Furriers (St. John, New Brunswick), 1912-1913 (Box-folder 11 / 34)
    - R.J. Mancantelli (Toronto, Ont.), 1909-1912 (Box-folder 11 / 35)
    - Maa-Man (correspondents include Maas and Steffen, Fred Mabee, S.M. Mace, Roderick R. Macleary, J.W. Maddux, George A. Madson, Magness Brothers Auctioneers, Stephen A. Mahaffey, H.W. Main, Maine Agricultural Experiment Station, Claude Makin, Malin-Yates Company, John B. Maling, L.C. Mallory, A. L. Malott), 1907-1928 (Box-folder 11 / 36)
    - Thomas A. Marlow (Helena, Mont., see also A.B. Cook and Company subgroup), 1909-1922 (Box-folder 12 / 1)
    - Marcus M. Marshall (Marshall Properties Holding Company, Los Angeles, Calif.), 1927 (Box-folder 12 / 2)
    - Matador Land and Cattle Company (Trinidad, Colo.; includes William Kerr, John McBain, M.J. Reilly), 1918-1922 (Box-folder 12 / 3)
    - John Matthews (Townsend, Mont.), 1919-1922 (Box-folder 12 / 4)
    - Mayo Clinic (Rochester, Minn.), 1925-1928 (Box-folder 12 / 5)
    - Mar-May (correspondents include Marion Steam Shovel Company, Ole Markuson, Stephen Marmant, Marrion Well Drilling Company, Marshall Field and Company, Henry W. Marshall, Marshall-Wells Hardware Company, Martinsdale Live Stock Company, Joe Marzen, Joe Mason, G.L. Mathews, Ernest R. May, Theodore Mayer), 1906, 1011-1928 (Box-folder 12 / 6)
    - McCaull-Dinsmore Company (Helena, Mont.), 1922-1923 (Box-folder 12 / 7)
    - Frank W. McConnell (Dallas and El Paso, Tex.), 1909-1917 (Box-folder 12 / 8)
    - W. Milton McCoy (Circle V Ranch, Big Horn, Wyo.), 1925-1927 (Box-folder 12 / 9)
    - Warren T. McCray (Orchard Lake Stock Farm, Kentland, Ind.), 1917-1921 (Box-folder 12 / 10)
    - McA-McC (correspondents include A.B. McAdam, C.W. McCampbell, H.E. McCausland, Harry J. McClean, Mike and Thomas McCormick, Charles McCrea, Sen. J.P. McCumber), 1909-1928 (Box-folder 12 / 11)
    - K.C. McFarland (Tacoma, Wash.), 1914-1915 (Box-folder 12 / 12)
    - John McGinnis (Butte, Mont.), 1908-1918 (Box-folder 12 / 13)
    - B.J. McIntire (Kalispell, Mont.), 1908-1909 (Box-folder 12 / 14)